Gustavo Pedroni

gstvpedronil@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/gustavo-pedroni/en https://github.com/gustavopedroni

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Working for more than 5 years in development. I have solid knowledge in Python and Node.js, as well as great knowledge in Amazon Web Services and good development practices. Always very creative, I love to be learning new ways to solve old problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Node.js Developer

At App Bipp

October 2020 - March 2021

- Full stack development using Node.js, Adonis.js, React and MySQL for Dashboard of a Mobile App;
- Applying CI/CD with GitHub Actions;
- Python Scripting development for publishing automation and pre-registration of apps on Google and Apple;

PHP Developer

At <u>Saga Sistemas</u>

March 2019 - July 2020

- Development of customized systems for company management using PHP and MySQL;
- Development of an authenticator system using Python, Django and PostgreSQL;
- API development of custom systems using Node.is and Express;
- Publications of systems on AWS, using EC2, RDS and ELB;

Python Developer

At Cake ERP

April 2015 - March 2018

- ERP development using Python, Pyramid and MySQL;
- Publications in AWS environments using Elastic Beanstalk and Lambda;
- Development of a Point of Sale using Python, Kivy, SQLite and MySQL;

EDUCATION

Technologist in System Analysis

UCS (University of Caxias do Sul) June 2017- Present

Technologist in System Development

CETEC

2013- 2016